

Tomás <u>Caputo</u>

Jr FrontEnd web <u>developer</u>

PERSONAL RESUME

Web application development student.

Focused on finding my first experience as a developer / layout designer, in wich I can provide adequate solutions towards FrontEnd development of static and dinamic web pages, learn new development environments and be part of an IT team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5 CSS3 (Flex Grids)
- Responsive web Design
- Preprocessor: SASS
- BootStrap 4 5
- JavaScript (Vanilla Ecma)
- GIT GitHub
- Figma Adobe Balsamiq
- WordPress
- Hardware technical knowledge

Practice in transfer of MockUp to code, development of responsive websites for each type of screen, implementation of new functionalities.

CONTACT

- Oleiros, A Coruña
- Tomas.caputo@hotmail.com
- 04 / 03 / 1996
- Nationality: Italian / Argentine
- NIE, CUE (Yes) NUSS (Yes)
- Town change: Yes

EDUCATION

Universidad da Vinci. ARG

Web application development | 2021 - 2023

• Currently, studying technical degree in web application development, online modality. (In process of change to Spanish FP2).

Educación IT, ARG

FrontEnd web developer course | 2021 - Present

• Studying complementary course in FrontEnd development.

☐

CoderHouse, ARG

Web developer | May 2021 - July 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

4 years experience working in companies in different areas of customer service and administration.

• Ski Lift Operator

Vail Resorts, USA | December 2019 - March 2020

• Commertial administrative

NRG Motors, ARG | January 2018 - July 2019

• Administrative assistant - Bartender Barras móviles Juan B, ARG | June 2015 - December 2017

I will apply organizational, communication and teamwork skills learned and developed in my previous work experiences.

PORTFOLIO / LINKEDIN





LANGUAGES

• English, proficiency B.2

